

Guilherme Fidélio

Designer focused on visual representations and the power they exercise in the user experience. I bring design process knowledge, research and UX to create interfaces that are not only aesthetically pleasing, but that talk to the user and make their daily lives more comfortable.

guilhermefidelio.com.br Guilhermeh1996@gmail.com (11) 9 5967-5135 linkedin.com/in/guilherme-fidélio/ behance.net/guilhermehff dribbble.com/guilhermefidelio

Experience

Product Designer @ Hubster

Dec. 2019 – Jan. 2020

Responsible for establishing the Design System - typography, iconography, colour palettes, grids and various elements of the interface - and unification of the styles present on the platform. Creation of marketing pieces and development of new web pages to attract new leads, with the establishment and monitoring of statistics.

UX/UI Designer @ Apple Developer Academy Feb. 2018 – Dec. 2019

Development of applications focused on the iOS platform. I participated in projects from its conception until its launch, with market research, usability tests and creation of the branding and screens for each application.

Academic Researcher @ Senac São Paulo Jan.2018 – Jan.2019

Research focused on the influence generated upon players in electronic games without their knowledge. Together with other members of the research group, I used this knowledge to explore the possibilities that chatbots offer as a means of information and design. Articles developed in this group were presented in Argentina, the United States and adapted for a book chapter on design systems.

Education

- Digital Design @ Senac University CenterFeb. 2016 Dec. 2019
- Digital Design @ Anhembi MorumbiFeb. 2015 Dec. 2015
- Graphic Design @ Escola Panamericana de Arte e Design
 Feb. 2013 – Dec. 2014

